<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <UB_Seal_TribalKidNomad.title>nomad</UB_Seal_TribalKidNomad.title>
  <UB_Seal_TribalKidNomad.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s parents were wanderers. They didn't belong to any tribe and travelled from village to village. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to forage for food and followed them on fishing and hunting trips when winter was harsh. Unfortunately, [PAWN_pronoun] never really socialized with other children, and preferred to stay with [PAWN_possessive] parents whenever they were staying in a settlement.</UB_Seal_TribalKidNomad.description>
  <UB_Seal_Savage.title>savage</UB_Seal_Savage.title>
  <UB_Seal_Savage.description>Found very young in the wild by tribespeople, [PAWN_nameDef]'s origins are unknown. Acting like an animal, [PAWN_pronoun] was taken by a family and taught to talk and interact with fellow tribe members.\n\nIf [PAWN_pronoun] is properly integrated into human society and doesn't remember [PAWN_possessive] time in the wilderness, [PAWN_pronoun] still struggles to socialize and often acts strangely to the eyes of other people.</UB_Seal_Savage.description>
  <UB_Seal_PebblePainter.title>pebble painter</UB_Seal_PebblePainter.title>
  <UB_Seal_PebblePainter.titleShort>painter</UB_Seal_PebblePainter.titleShort>
  <UB_Seal_PebblePainter.description>[PAWN_nameDef] loved to paint rocks. [PAWN_pronoun] collected pebbles and used various dyes to create small images on their surface. [PAWN_pronoun] kept [PAWN_possessive] best works in [PAWN_possessive] collection, safe from the other kids that might want to steal one.</UB_Seal_PebblePainter.description>
  <UB_Seal_TribalKidTender.title>tender</UB_Seal_TribalKidTender.title>
  <UB_Seal_TribalKidTender.description>Learning from [PAWN_possessive] parents, [PAWN_nameDef] helped them heal injured warriors or sick people. [PAWN_pronoun] cleaned the wounds and sew them close again, or prepared various infusions.\n\nDeaths occured frequently, and each time, [PAWN_nameDef] couldn't chase the sad thoughts from [PAWN_possessive] mind.</UB_Seal_TribalKidTender.description>
  <UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.title>shaman apprentice</UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.title>
  <UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.titleShort>shaman</UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.titleShort>
  <UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was found very young in the wilderness and was taken by a local tribe. People never trusted [PAWN_objective] and believed [PAWN_pronoun] was some sort of monstrous night creature in hiding. [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually adopted and raised by a shaman, from which [PAWN_pronoun] learned to mix herbs and talk to the spirits.</UB_Seal_ShamanApprentice.description>
</LanguageData>